http://www.survival.com/library/orders-and-deals/privacy-statement/

HomeMeet KarenLegacy of Ron HoodVideosWoodsmasterWM1 – Spark Based Fire StartingWM2 – Survival Shelter SelectionWM3 – Making and Using your Outdoor Survival KitWM4 – Primitive Navigation and Wilderness Travel TechniquesWM5 – Traps and TrappingWM6 – Primitive Weapons TechnologyWM7 – Jungle Living SkillsWM8 – The Fundamentals of TrackingWM9 – Primitive Knife MakingWM10 – Survival CampingWM11 – SOLO: The Quest for SurvivalWM12 – Arid Land – Vehicle SurvivalWM13 – Desert Survival; On FootWM14 – Crafts for the fieldWM15 – Sticks, Stoves and StitchesWM16 – Buffalo Butchers; Meat and Material from Large GameWM17 – Buffalo Butchers: The Final ChapterWM18 – Bronze 1 Molding, Copying and CastingWM19 – Bronze 2 – The Home FoundryWM20 – Bronze 3 – The Final StepsWM21 – Family Camping V1Cave CookingCC1 – In The BushCC2 – Going DutchCC3 – Frocks, Fat & FoodCC4 – Messin’ with MeatCC5 – BB Primitive CookingUrban MasterUM Vol 1 – The HomeUM Vol 2 – Away from HomeTelly AwardsLetterman and KarenSurvival BasicsWhy Video?DVDCustomer CommentsMagazine ReviewsSponsorsSports AfieldYouTubeRonzbronzeAvailableArchivesAdventure TeamH2K CampsAnyplace Wild TVArticlesA Little HistoryAndragogyCrappin’Eating BugsFish PoisonsKaren SoloLadies in the WoodsSolo Gear ListThe FirebedToons By FrikTrapper ThoughtsWilderness ForgeBest LinksOther LinksBlades for the FieldAnacondaFehrmanHood HunterKhukuri ReviewSiegle BladesSimonich KanjiThe ATAXTOPS KnivesTrace RinaldiBook IntroChapter 1Chapter 2Chapter 3Chapter 4BooksGear ResourcesOutdoor SchoolsDavid AllowayMarty SimonSalmon Outdoor SchoolSchool of Self-RelianceSurvival KitsBESTBig TargetDUSKEric’s KitFrediver’s KitMOSSSASSTC PorterThe Micro KitThe Mini KitWhy Prepare?Preparedness 101CBR FactsPreparednessKaren’s ArticleUrban TrappingHollywood WisdomHoodlums ForumOrders and DealsPrivacy StatementReturnsContact Us
Home » Archives » Orders and Deals » Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
Hoods
Woods respects the privacy of our customers. All information provided
to Hoods Woods by our customers is used strictly for internal purposes
by Hoods Woods.Should you choose to sign up for our mailing list, Hoods
Woods will NOT supply your contact information to any partner or
sponsor unless the option to do so is enabled and approved by you.
If
you place an order through the Hoods Woods on-line ordering system,
your transaction is fully encrypted and the information sent to us will
enjoy the same protections as members of our mailing list. Your
personal information is stored on a stand alone computer system that is
fully encrypted and secured and has NO access to the Internet. (If
someone wants to TRY to hack it they have to get through us first.)
We do not sell, rent, or disclose personal information to any third parties under any other circumstances.
If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy of your information at Hoods Woods, please send contact us for more information.
January 7, 2010Karen Hood
Survivology 101
This domain may be for sale. Click here to inquire further.
©2018 Survival.com, All Rights Reserved. Any unauthorized use, reproduction or duplication in part or in whole of any images, videos or audio on this site is an infringement of copyright law and will be dealt with accordingly.
If you would like to use any of our images or videos for any reason, please contact us on our contact page and we can discuss it further. Thank you.
